http://www.suffolk.edu/about/mission-history/policies-procedures/internet-privacy-policy

This website uses cookies as well as similar tools and technologies to understand visitors' experiences. By continuing to use this website, you consent to Suffolk University's usage of cookies and similar technologies, in accordance with the Suffolk University Cookie Policy.
Close
Skip Navigation
Find a Program
After typing a search term, you may arrow down to select common related searches.
Accounting Programs
Advertising, Public Relations, & Social Media
Art & Design
Big Data & Business Analytics Programs
Biochemistry
Biology
Business Economics
Business Law & Ethics
Environment & Sustainability
Executive MBA (EMBA)
Finance
Financial Wealth Management
Healthcare Administration Programs
History
Information Systems & Operations Management
Interdisciplinary Programs
Juris Doctor
Management & Entrepreneurship
Law Programs
Search:
Home
About
Academics
Admission
Student Life
Alumni
COVID-19 Info
Visit
Internet Privacy Policy
Suffolk University is committed to preserving your privacy. Please read the following privacy policy to understand how we use and protect the information from those visiting and using the University web site. By using the University website you consent to the collection, retention and use of your personal information in accordance with the terms of this policy. If you do not agree with the use of personal information as described in this Privacy Policy or any changes to it, you should not use or access the website or any features of the website. The types of information we collect may vary depending on the specific site you visit or application you use. Accordingly, this Privacy Statement is intended to be a general statement and may be supplemented by more specific privacy policies that pertain to personal information exclusively associated with a specific department, unit or function.
This privacy policy informs you about how and for what purpose(s) we process personal data in connection with your visit to, and use of, our website. Any changes that we make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page.
What Information do we collect?
We limit the collection of information to that which is required in order to provide services to you. When you use our website we may collect, store and process certain information about you, including:
How you use the website and any information you provide on this website in the form of email, feedback forms, survey answers, post or otherwise send to us.
Personal details which you provide by registering with us or submitting an inquiry (this can include your name, contact details and email address).
Information we collect automatically
It is possible to use our website without providing any personal data. However, please be aware that we automatically collect information such as:
the areas of the website you visit
information about your computer, such as which browser you are using, your network location, the type of connection you are using
Cookies
When you visit our Website, we use “cookies” and other tracking technologies like “web beacons” to allow us to remember your user preferences, to maximize the performance of our website, and to enhance and personalize your experience. For more information on how this site uses cookies please visit our Cookie Policy.
Do Not Track
Do-Not-Track is a public-private initiative that has developed a “flag” or signal that an Internet user may activate in the user’s browser software to notify websites that the user does not wish to be “tracked” by third-parties as defined by the initiative. The online community has not agreed on what actions, if any, should be taken by the websites that receive the “do not track” signal, and therefore Do-Not-Track is not yet standardized. Our website does not alter its behavior or change its services when it receives a “do-not-track” flag or signal from your browser.
Social Network Widgets
Our website may include social network sharing widgets that may provide information to their associated social networks or third-parties about your interactions with our web pages that you visit, even if you do not click on or otherwise interact with the plug-in or widget. Information is transmitted from your browser and may include an identifier assigned by the social network or third party, information about your browser type, operating system, device type, IP address, and the URL of the web page where widget appears. If you use social network tools or visit social networking sites, you should read their privacy disclosures, to learn what information they collect, use, and share.
Information from Children
Suffolk University does not intend to collect any information directly from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, you may use the Suffolk University website only with the involvement of a parent or guardian. If you believe we have inadvertently collected information about your child, please email the Suffolk University Service Desk and we will attempt to delete the information from Suffolk University’s systems.
How do we use your information?
We use your information to:
enable us to supply you with the goods, services and information which you have requested
ensure that content from the website is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer
analyze the information we collect so that we can administer, support, improve, and develop the website
provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we believe may interest you, unless you have indicated otherwise
notify you about changes to our service
How do we share your information?
Other than sharing your information with other appropriate university personnel and units to ensure the quality, functionality, and security of our website, or manage your relationship with us, we will not disclose personally identifiable information about your use of the site except under the following circumstances:
With your prior written (including email) consent
When we have given you clear notice that we will disclose information that you voluntarily provide
With appropriate external parties, such as law enforcement agencies, in order to investigate and respond to suspected violations of law or university policy. Any such disclosures shall comply with all applicable laws and university policies.
Subscriptions
For e-mail notices or subscribers to a newsletter, you may unsubscribe at any time by notifying Suffolk University at the address provided in such e-mail notice or newsletter.
Security
Our websites and our computer systems have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of personal data held by us. All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Any payment transactions will be encrypted. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our websites, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.
Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our websites; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we receive your information, we will use reasonable safeguards consistent with best practices of the data being stored to maintain the security of that information on our systems.
In addition, we will comply with all applicable federal, state and local laws regarding the privacy and security of the information.
Links to other websites
Our websites may contain links to other websites which are outside the University's control and are not covered by this privacy policy. We are not responsible for the privacy policies of any such linked websites. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.
How to Request Access to or Deletion of Information and Files Pertaining to You
You have the right to request access to information and files pertaining to you. You also have the right to request that information pertaining to you be removed from Suffolk University systems and files. You may exercise these rights by contacting the office below that is most appropriate to your role at the University. We require that such requests be made in writing and include the following information:
Your name and role (applicant, student, or employee);
contact information, including your email and postal addresses;
the item(s) of information you wish to access or want removed; and
the reason for requesting access to, or removal of, the information.
Undergraduate Applicants may contact the Office of Undergraduate Admission.
Graduate Applicants may contact the Office of Graduate Admission.
Law School Applicants may contact the Office of Law Admission.
Students may contact the Office of the Registrar.
Employees may contact the Office of Human Resources Management.
There are some instances where the University may deny a request to remove information. For example, the University may decline to remove the following types of information, including, but not limited to:
information required to be maintained by the University as part of student or employment records, or pursuant to local, state or Federal law, statute or other regulation, or in performance of contractual obligations.
information compiled in reasonable anticipation of, or for use in a civil, criminal or administrative action or proceeding.
The University will generally respond to requests no later than thirty (30) days after receipt. If a request is denied, we will send a written explanation detailing the reason for the denial and a notification of your right to file a written statement of disagreement. The University may also provide a right to have the denial reviewed. If the University is unable to act within thirty (30) days, we may extend that time by no more than an additional sixty (60) days. If we need to extend this time, we will notify you of the delay and the date by which we will complete action on your request.
Contacting Suffolk University regarding this policy
Policy: Web Privacy
Email the Suffolk University Service Desk
US mail: Suffolk University, 8 Ashburton Place, Boston, MA 02108
Users Located in the European Union
If you are located in the European Union, please see here for additional information about ways that certain Suffolk University Madrid and Suffolk University Boston entities, including this website, may collect, use, and share information about you.
Changes to the Privacy Statement
The Privacy Statement is subject to change, and the revision date will be noted here. We encourage users to regularly review the Privacy Statement for any changes.
2020-01-13
